If you all want to know about Aditya Birla Sun Life
Insurance Company Limited's Guaranteed
Milestone Plan
in detail along with eligibility criteria and
benefits, then check the description of today's video.
You will
find the link to the Guaranteed Milestone Plan video in the video description.  As
you all know, every day every video on the channel
comes according to your questions, suggestions and comments.  So
please like and share the video.
Subscribe to the channel and turn on all notification
bells so that
you get the latest videos.  Hello everyone,
you all are very welcome.  You're watching You the
Real.  I am your personal advisor
Amit Raj Sharma.  In today's video we will
learn about the surrender value of Guaranteed Milestone Plan of Aditya Birla Sun Life Insurance Company Limited as per the comment of Mr.  If you have
this plan and have
paid premiums continuously for at least 2 years, only then can you
get guaranteed surrender value.
To calculate the guaranteed surrender value,
you need to multiply the guaranteed surrender value factor with the
total premium paid and the
base premium paid.  Then whatever amount of
Accrued Guaranteed Addition is collected,
it has a separate Guaranteed Under Value Factor.
It is multiplied and added to it.  Let us
take an example in this manner.  Let us
assume that Mr. Neha is
30 years old.  He took the Guaranteed Milestone Plan of Aditya Birla Sun
Life Insurance Company Limited.
Took a policy term of 20 years.  Took a premium payment term of 10 years.  The
sum assured he chose was ₹7.5
lakh.  So in such a situation he would be paying a premium of ₹500 annually.
Right?  Now suppose
that Shrima
wants to surrender the policy after completion of 5 years.  I do
n't want to pay any further premium.
So what does the plan say in such a situation?   The
plan says that if you pay a base premium of ₹00 per annum
and the sum assured is ₹75
lakh, then a
guaranteed addition of ₹8,860 will accumulate
in the policy every year.  So after completion of 5 years
Rs.  You would have already paid the premium of Rs. 1 lakh
and there will be a
guaranteed addition of Rs. 1,44,300.   If it is a
plan with guaranteed returns, you will find out by
checking the benefit illustration of the policy bond.
So here the
Guaranteed Surrender Value factor
applied on the paid premium will be 50%
and the Guaranteed Surrender Value factor
applied on the earned Guaranteed Addition will be
26%.  That means
we will take out 50% of ₹5 lakh and add
26% of ₹144300 to it.  So the guaranteed
surrender value will
come to ₹162518.  They will get this.
The policy will be closed.  In this way you
can calculate the surrender value.
Now here we can directly see the chart
that shows the percentage of total premium paid.
Which premium paid?  Base premium.
Percentage of Earned Guaranteed Edition.
Yes, this is the table of surrender value factor.
20 years positive, 10 years premium
payment term taken.  5 years have been completed.
So here
comes our guaranteed under value of 50% applicable on the premium.
26% for Accurate Guaranteed Edition
This PDF is already available on the telgram channel where you are seeing it on the top of the screen.  Will get it.  The
link
is in the description of the video.  Check your policy
bond.  You will get it in that too.  The
maximum loan amount available is 85% of the surrender value
and the interest rate is 1.25%,
which is not fixed.   It will keep
changing with time.  Thank you all
for patiently watching the video till the end.
Like, share the video,
subscribe to the channel and turn on all the notification
bells.  Understand one thing yourself.
Explain to others also that insurance is a
protection.  Never take incomplete protection.
What topic do you want the next video to be about
?  Please do tell in the comment section.
Thank you.